2knowmyself.com 2016-11-19

# Privacy policy | 2KnowMySelf

The privacy of our visitors to www.2knowmyself.com is important to us.  
At www.2knowmyself.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit www.2knowmyself.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**We never store Personal information**  
2knowmyself.com doesn’t store any of your personal information when you make a purchase or when you visit the site. Your credit card number, your address, email ..etc are never stored on the site under any case. 

In case you subscribed to our email list you will get emails on the email you entered and you will get addressed by the name you chose for yourself whether it was a real or fake name. The email management process is done by Aweber, one of the most famous email management companies, and you can opt out any time.

**Sever Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

This information is never sold to any party and is only used to troubleshoot and maintain the website.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on www.2knowmyself.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. 

This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

We sometimes use cookies to personalize content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyze our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our advertising and analytics partners (Google Adsense and Google Analytics) who may combine it with other information you’ve provided to them or they’ve collected from your use of their services.

Cookies cannot be used to find your name, email address, or anything that is uniquely identifying about you, unless you provide that information. We use cookies for those applications that require us to keep track of information to customize results.

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

**Google Analytics**  
Like most websites 2knowmyself.com uses Google Analytics software which is a piece of code that anonymously tracks the number of visitors to the site, the page views and the other related metrics.

Google Analytics doesn't collect any private information about you such as your email, name or address but instead it is just used to measure the site's performance in terms of the number of visitors and other metrics.

**Purchases from 2knowmyself**  
2knowmyself never saves your credit card information nor we even have access to at. All sales on 2knowmyself happen through world wide recognized payment gateways such as Clickbank and 2checkout. Both of those gateways never give us access to your credit card information.

After a purchase happens however we are passed the email address you used to make the purchase in addition to your basic info such as your name and country in order for us to be able to send you the product(s) and provide proper customer service.

If you have any question related to privacy please Contact us right away and you will get an answer within 24 hours.
